hddgames.com 2018-05-10

# Privacy Policy - HDDgames.com - Full Pc Games Download Free

**Privacy Policy**

 **What information do we collect?**

Our site can be viewed anonymously, we do not ask for any personal information to access the content.

However if you choose to register on the site or forums you will be asked to enter a username, a valid email address and a password, the rest of the information is completely optional and up to you to fill in.

We do not share your email or personal data with anyone.

 **What do we use your information for?**

We may use your contact email address to comunicate with you if we need to.

It is kept in the database to keep record of the users, we do not mass email our users, you however will receive an email after registering and when you get a private message but those settings can be disabled.

 **How do we protect your information?**

This website uses the latest version of the software needed to run the site: Apache, PHP, MySQL, WordPress and PHPBB to ensure a safe environment for our users.

Your personal data is not visible to us, we don’t have access to your password, only you do.

 **Do we use cookies?**

We use a cookie to keep you logged in on the website/forums if you choose the option “remember me” while loggining in.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell or trade your information with anyone.

 **Terms and Conditions**

For legal requests visit our DMCA Disclaimers page at:

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we need to change our privacy police the changes will be seen on this page only.

 **Contacting Us**

If you have further questions read the contact page.
